[{"question": " wow, this is so cool, you guys. the entire city is blacked out!", "answer": " mom says it's all of manhattan, parts of brooklyn and queens, and they have no idea when it's coming back on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " wow, you guys, this is big.", "answer": "  pants and a sweater? why, mom? who am i gonna meet in a blackout? power company guys? eligible looters? could we talk about this later? ok.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " oh my god, it's that victoria's secret model. something... something goodacre.", "answer": "  hi mom, it's jill.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " she's right, it's jill. jill goodacre. oh my god. i am trapped in an atm vestibule with jill goodacre!  is it a vestibule? maybe it's an atrium. oh, yeah, that is the part to focus on, you idiot!", "answer": "  yeah, i'm fine. i'm just stuck at the bank, in an atm vestibule.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " jill says vestibule... i'm going with vestibule.", "answer": "  i'm fine. no, i'm not alone... i don't know, some guy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " hi everyone.", "answer": " and officiating at tonight's blackout, is rabbi tribbiani.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " well, chandler's old roomate was jewish, and these are the only candles we have, so... happy chanukah, everyone.", "answer": "  eww, look. ugly naked guy lit a bunch of candles.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " you're definitely scaring here.", "answer": "  would you like to call somebody?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " hello?", "answer": " hey, it's me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": "  it's chandler!  are you ok?", "answer": " yeah, i'm fine.  i'm trppd in an atm vstbl wth jll gdcr.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " i'm trppd... in an atm vstbl... wth jll gdcr!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " i have no idea what you just said.", "answer": "  put joey on the phone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " what's up man?", "answer": " i'm trppd... in an atm vstbl... wth jll gdcr.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " alright, somebody.", "answer": " ok, i'll go. ok, senior year of college... on a pool table.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " whoooaa!", "answer": " that's my sister.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " ok... my weirdest place would have to be... the women's room on the second floor of the new york city public library.", "answer": " oh my god! what were you doing in a library?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " phoebs, what about you?", "answer": " oh... milwaukee.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " um... ross?", "answer": " disneyland, 1989, 'it's a small world after all.'", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " no way!", "answer": " the ride broke down. so, carol and i went behind a couple of those mechanical dutch children... then they fixed the ride, and we were asked never to return to the magic kingdom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " oh, rachel.", "answer": " oh come on, i already went.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " you did not go!", "answer": " come on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " oh, alright. the weirdest place would have to be... ... oh, the foot of the bed.", "answer": " step back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " i just never had a relationship with that kind of passion, you know, where you have to have somebody right there, in the middle of a theme park.", "answer": " well, it was the only thing to do there that didn't have a line.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " there, well, see? barry wouldn't even kiss me on a miniature golf course.", "answer": " come on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " no, he said we were holding up the people behind us.", "answer": "  and you didn't marry him because...?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " i mean, do you think there are people who go through life never having that kind of...", "answer": " probably. but you know, i'll tell you something. passion is way overrated.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " yeah right.", "answer": " it is. eventually, it kind of... burns out. but hopefully, what you're left with is trust, and security, and... well, in the case of my ex-wife, lesbianism. so, you know, for all of those people who miss out on that passion... thing, there's all that other good stuff.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": "  ok.", "answer": " but, um... i don't think that's going to be you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " you don't.", "answer": " uh-uh. see, i see.... big passion in your future.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " mmmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " you do?", "answer": " i do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " it's never gonna happen.", "answer": "  what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " you and rachel.", "answer": "  what?  why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " because you waited too long to make your move, and now you're in the friend zone.", "answer": " no, no, no. i'm not in the zone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " ross, you're mayor of the zone.", "answer": " i'm taking my time, alright? i'm laying the groundwork. yeah. i mean, every day i get just a little bit closer to...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " priesthood! look ross, i'm telling you, she has no idea what you're thinking. if you don't ask her out soon you're going to end up stuck in the zone forever.", "answer": " i will, i will. see, i'm waiting for the right moment.  what? what, now?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " shhhh!", "answer": " what are you shushing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " we're shushing... because... we're trying to hear something. listen.  don't you hear that?", "answer": " ahhhh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " see?", "answer": " huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " would you like some gum?", "answer": " um, is it sugarless?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": "  sorry, it's not.", "answer": " oh, then no thanks. what the hell was that? mental note: if jill goodacre offers you gum, you take it. if she offers you mangled animal carcass, you take it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": "  ok, here goes.", "answer": " are you going to do it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " i'm going to do it.", "answer": " do you want any help?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " you come out there, you're a dead man.", "answer": " good luck, man.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " thanks.  ok.", "answer": " ok.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " hey, where are you going?", "answer": " outside.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " you can't go out there.", "answer": " why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " because of... the reason.", "answer": " and that would be?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " i, um, can't tell you.", "answer": " joey, what's going on?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " ok, you've got to promise that you'll never, ever tell ross that i told you.", "answer": " about what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " he's planning your birthday party.", "answer": " oh my god! i love him!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": "  you'd better act surprised.", "answer": " about what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " my surprise party!", "answer": " what surprise party?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " oh stop it. joey already told me.", "answer": " well, he didn't tell me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " hey, don't look at me. this is ross's thing.", "answer": " this is so typical. i'm always the last one to know everything.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " no, you are not. we tell you stuff.", "answer": " yuh-huh! i was the last one to know when chandler got bitten by the peacock at the zoo. i was the last one to know when you had a crush on joey when he was moving in.  looks like i was second to last.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " hmmm... this is so nice.", "answer": " ok, i have a question. well, actually, it's not so much a question as.. more of a general wondering... ment.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " ok.", "answer": " ok. here goes. for a while now, i've been wanting to, um....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " yes, yes, that's right...", "answer": " oh, look at the little cat!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " sorry, that was wax.", "answer": " oh, poor little tooty is scared to death. we should find his owner.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " why don't we just put 'poor little tooty' out in the hall?", "answer": " during a blackout? he'd get trampled!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": "  oh no, the mendels, they hate all living things, right?", "answer": " oh.  hi. we just found this cat and we're looking for the owner.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " er, yeah, it's mine.", "answer": "  he seems to hate you. are you sure?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " yeah, it's my cat. give me my cat.", "answer": " wait a minute. what's his name?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " ehhhh... b-buttons.", "answer": " bob buttons?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " mmm. bob buttons. here, bob buttons.", "answer": "  oooh! you are a very bad man!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": "  lucky sixes....", "answer": "  everybody, this is paolo. paolo, i want you to meet my friends. this is monica.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": "  hi!", "answer": " and joey....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " and ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": "", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": "  he doesn't speak much english.", "answer": "  monopoly!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " look at that!", "answer": "  so, um... where did paolo come from?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " oh... italy, i think.", "answer": " no, i mean tonight, in the building. suddenly. into our lives.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " well, the cat... the cat turned out to be paolo's cat!", "answer": " that, that is funny... .... and rachel keeps touching him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " alright. i looked all over the building and i couldn't find the kitty anywhere.", "answer": " oh, i found him. he was paolo's cat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " ah! well! there you go! last to know again! and i'm guessing... since nobody told me... this is paolo.", "answer": " ah, paolo, this is phoebe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " my god, you're choking!  that better?", "answer": "  yes... thank you. that was... that was....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " wha-what did he say that was so funny?", "answer": " i have absolutely no idea.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " that's... that's classic.", "answer": "  oh my god, you guys, what am i doing? what am i doing? this is so un-me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " i know, i just want to bite his bottom lip.  but i won't.", "answer": " god, the first time he smiled at me... those three seconds were more exciting than three weeks in bermuda with barry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " you know, did you ride mopeds? 'cause i've heard... ... oh, i see... it's not about that right now. ok.", "answer": " y'know, i know it's totally superficial and we have absolutely nothing in common, and we don't even speak the same language but goooooooddddddd....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " paolo. hi.", "answer": " ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " listen. um, listen. something you should... know... um, rachel and i... we're kind of a thing.", "answer": " thing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " thing, yes. thing.", "answer": " ah, you... have the sex?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " no, no, no. technically the... sex is not... being had, but that's... see, that's not the point. see, um, the point is that... rachel and i should be, er, together. you know, and if you get in the.... um...", "answer": " bed?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " no, no, that's not where i was going. er, if you get in the... way, of us becoming a thing, then i would be, well, very sad.", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " yeah! se vice?", "answer": " si.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " so you do know a little english.", "answer": " poco... a leetle.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " do you know the word crapweasel?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " chandler, we've been here for an hour doing this! now watch, it's easy.", "answer": " ok.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " thank you.", "answer": " thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " kinda... spooky without any lights.", "answer": "  bwah-hah-hah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " oh.. oh... oh.", "answer": " hey ross. this probably isn't the best time to bring it up, but you have to throw a party for monica.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " well, this has been fun.", "answer": " yes. yes, thanks for letting me use your phone... and for saving my life.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}]